Sup everyone, T5 here with a very
special video. Today we're back again
with the Wings Club. The Magic is back.
Is the magic back yet? Not quite, but
maybe this episode will turn things
around. Like, I don't think it will, but
I haven't watched it yet. I mean, do do
you wipe your ass before you [__] Like,
that's the show principle all wings
clubbers like us live by. Amarat.
Now, this episode it's like called Into
the Woods. So, as you can probably guess
from the tow alone, it's like about a
cami trip and [__] But there's like one
problem, [__] Like the wings of the
wings of they can't use the magic
anymore because like the [__] Miss
Faraganda pulled in last episode. All of
the other fairy [__] like you know
like blooms and [__] Like they all
start like it's the end of the world up
in this [__] But like aren't you guys
like 16, 17? Like you had schooling have
to do basic ass magic. Like you were
surprised when a little leprechaun like
pulled up show and tell yesterday like
with his little house. He probably
pulled out his fat ass. Like, do these
guys not know how to live life without
any form of magic? I still I'm I guess
Stella did use a spell to repair
destroyed bathroom like all the way back
in episode one. So, maybe they can't
wait didn't witches like start going to
the fairy school because like the witch
schools destroyed like 16 years ago. Why
did they just repair that one? That's
just a ball. So, the wings club or they
think they can't go back. We don't have
access to magic, but they realize they
have to go because it catch a school
test and no one wants to fail that. So,
like, let's pack it up, [__] The
Winks Clubers and [__] like they head
out into the woods and I can't be the
only one who thinks they look like the
Turbo Power Ranger, right? Like the
color coined everything. Like, there's
like red, blue, green. That is the Turbo
Power Rangers. Now, I I'm gonna be real
with you guys. Like I was getting a bit
scared during this power because they're
in the middle of the woods and I could
only think of one thing that could
possibly out there. Like I was feeling
for my life. I mean we already saw one.
What stop us from running through a
whole ass village of these [__] You
know what? We good. So we good. We good
so far. Like so I'm just going to stop
talking. He hasn't been up yet. I'm not
going to jinx it. Now it cuts to all the
bad [__] and Dam is the two I guess.
Like they're just hanging out in the
bottom again. Is that like the secret
hideout? That's stupid. Like what if the
teachers or students just walk in while
Vexius is just pooping in the corner?
Does he just kill them? Or does he just
like [__] in the dark hoping they don't
smell it? Like I I bet I bet if you let
a fart or some really runny [__] that
splash on the floor, he would have no
choice but to end their life. That would
make for a really good episode. Like I
like Vexus. The part where he poops out,
pull smoke sideways. That That was weird
though. That was weird. Thankfully, it's
just the tricks Damian who wander in so
he doesn't have to kill them. Instead,
he gets mad because he still doesn't
have Bloom's f house and he tells the
tricks to haul ass because like they're
taking forever. But like I don't blame
them. It's like it's Damian who keeps
messing things up. Like Aussie, Stormy,
and Dosy, they're bad [__] They can
and I mean M. They can do no wrong.
Unlike the Wink Club who's out in the
for seeing songs and being weirdly gay,
this [__] who works as as like a school
supervisor is like watching over the
winks to make sure they don't get like
more about wild animal since they can't
use magic. And she just gets nuked by
AI. Oh my god, I love this [__] She is
the only kid in the show who doesn't
piss me off. Everyone else makes me go a
[__] Bloom squats down next to Techna
to stop bullying her saying she be like
because she's shy and hates to be in
groups. Like, did I mention Bloom was a
[__] There is this really weird moment
where Stella just she just looks
crosseyed for an uncomfy long time and
does a damn thing. She's just like
looking at us like can she see us? The
scene then switches something that makes
me feel extremely privileged to have
witnessed before I die like and that is
the specialist on hoverboards. They're
just like blown out at the local town
allstar sports like they're playing
laser tag and everything. It's actually
disappointing cuz this area honestly
even I was it looks so damn cool. Like
even the models don't look half bad in
this lighting. Like maybe the ads are
working on the wrong [__] Like because
I swear the quality actually jumps up a
bit when they're not forced to do
generic fail [__] Back in the forest,
Damian is being bullied by the tricks as
he should. He sucks balls. Oh my god.
Drag him through the mud. He is a piece
of ass. I hope he just falls in and we
never see him again. That would be
funny. That would make me laugh. The
tricks begin attacking the wings and
Damian being a Say it with me class.
He's being what? He's being a [__] He
tries to stop because he doesn't want to
hurt his friends. Like, Damian, you're a
bad guy. Kill them. Stormy uses her
storm powers to blow him away.
Unfortunately, not to hold black onto
the ground. But that's good, too. By the
way, that one school employee agent is
like still frozen. You are going to tell
Miss Feraganda that the tricks are evil
and tried to commit to fail genocide on
you, right? You all going to tell her,
right?
So, the specialist show up and helps the
Wings Club again. The tricks out close
to killing the Wings Club again, and the
Wings Club barely escape again. One
thing I thought was pretty bitching,
though, was when I see something like
this huge ice ball thing. She was going
to nuke the Wings Club and kill them
all. Bloom just like throws a stick at a
flower causing a wall to or something to
fall on a attempt to freeze her but she
just breaks out eas because you know
she's an ass fairy I mean Bloom were you
not thinking I mean it did give Boom and
the other time to escape so I guess it
worked out but is that the best man you
can come with ghouls I got an idea let's
freeze the ice fail he's like do you
know how dumb that makes you sound like
I count it from the moment I fully
frozen to moving again 2 seconds that is
2 seconds. Why is she a badass? She
makes every kill a worse by existing. I
hate this. Miss [__] with the grad
school. She like says she received a
detailed report from her agent. And with
all due respect, no like she she didn't
unless by detailed report she means like
literally nothing because the tricks
again didn't get in trouble. Again,
Bloom is the one get yell at again. I
don't remember why. I just remember she
does. If I was Bloom, I'll be I would be
pooping my pants because the tricks
froze a school official now and they get
away with with this kind of stuff every
single day of their lives. Like why is
the grown ass man hiding in the bound
six whole episodes? I bet one day the
teachers walked in and thought, "Dad,
what is that smell?" And Vexius just had
his parents down poop in the corner
knowing they're too stupid to find him.
And let's be real, can you blame him?
I'd be doing it, too. Like anytime I had
to take a dump during class, I'd ask the
teacher if I could go take a smelly fat
[__] Like, do you think I'd go to the
school bathroom where I see and her gang
can bully my ass with her superior ass
powers? Uh-uh. If I was bloom, I'll be a
fair I'll be a fire fairy using the fire
escape and head into that bound. Now, we
know what the smell that had still
running for the hills all the way back
in episode one was. Vexi was Vexi was
was taking a shitty ass diarrhea dump.
Oh yeah, and the wings of G end up
getting the powers back through the
powers of friendship or something. I
don't really give a [__] I I just
realized the wings of pals. Why do they
suck? Like fire, water, plants?
Like that's okay, I guess. But
technology in a world of magic that acts
a shitload of computers, like music.
Like cool. What are you going to do do
with that? like seeing [__] who sleep
like what what even outs pals like I was
thinking it's like laugh but she keep
she keeps calling herself the fairy of
the sun and the moon like why why the
moon like at the end of the episode Dami
is still being moody [__] and Vexian is
his name Vexius or Vex I don't even know
anyway he's like watching from the
outhouse taking in another [__] so like
there you have it that was episode six I
didn't like it like I didn't like at all
I I'll give this like a two out of 10
You're like poetry. The crazy whirlwinds
blows dust from the corners of my mind.
Been long since last touched for the
first time. I thought it was crazy until
I reached out and saw your hand there
waiting for mine
like the stars had all aligned.
And I a
gravity. You don't have to try it. It's
just like a magnet. You have me. My
gravity.
Heat.
Gravity
like
it's like a bag.
Feel your energy
when our eyes touch. So familiar deep
inside
like you were already mine.
Sural to me how you make me feel wild
and calm at the same time.
Never felt so alive.
Thought I was crazy until I reached out
and saw your hand there waiting for
mine.
Like the stars at all.